{
    "qna": [
      {
        "question": "What is the brain of the computer?",
        "answer": "CPU"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of memory provides temporary storage for data?",
        "answer": "RAM"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of devices allow users to interact with computers?",
        "answer": "Input"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of devices display information or produce tangible results?",
        "answer": "Output"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many digits does binary code use?",
        "answer": "Two"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of devices are hard disk drives and solid-state drives?",
        "answer": "Storage"
      },
      {
        "question": "What system does computers operate using?",
        "answer": "Binary"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of computers are tailored to specific needs and applications?",
        "answer": "Personal"
      },
      {
        "question": "What has the internet transformed?",
        "answer": "Communication"
      },
      {
        "question": "What role are computers expected to play in the future?",
        "answer": "Significant"
      }
    ]
  }
  
